Guide to the Records of the Office of Library Administration RG.38.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series I: Alphabetical Subject Files, 1946-1995; 10.0
  - Social Work, School Of, 1974-1983 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Software/Micros, 1982-1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Space, 1962-1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Spanish- Portugese, Department of, 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Speciality Floors, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Specifications, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Spiegel, Sam, 1986-1989 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Staff- Professional Status and Privileges, 1946-1957 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Staff and Salary Survey, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Statistics- Questionaires Returned, 1963-1972 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Statistics- NYU Libraries Comparative Study, 1963-1969 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Status and Opinion of Library, 1969-1978 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Strasberg, 1982-1987 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Steel Stacks, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Stevens, 1989-1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Student Affairs II.2, 1981-1984 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Student Affairs II.2, Council for International Exchange of Scholars Fulbright Lecturing and Research Awards, 1981-1983 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Student Affairs II.2, Student Enrollment, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Student Affairs, Office of V.P., 1986 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Student Enrollment, 1962-1973 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Student Information Systems, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Student Information System Report, 1982-1983 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Student Life, Office of, 1985-1987 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Student Records and Registration- Students Guide to NYU, 1978-1987 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Student Senators Council, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Summer Sessions, 1978-1987 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Syren, Harold-Consultant, 1965-1973 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Tamiment, 1968-1969 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Tamiment Library, 1963-1971 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Task Force, University, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 40)
  - Task Force, University- Better Info for Student Choice, 1977 (Box 9, Folder 41)
  - Teacher Ed. Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Technical Services, 1965-1971 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Technical Services Annual Report, 1977 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Technical Services- Statistics, 1966-1972 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Telecommunications- Committee Meeting, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Telecommunication- Data Network System, 1982-1984 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Telecommunications- Dean Griffith's, 1982-1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Telecommunications Network at NYU, 1984 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Telecommunications- Technology in NYU Libraries, RLG and Distributed Processing, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Telephone System, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Telephones, 1963-1972 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Telephones, 1968-1973 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Tenth Anniversary, 1983-1984 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Theological Seminary, 1982-1983 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Theses, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Thomson Music Room, 1970-1971 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Tisch Hall Dedication, 1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Tisch School of Arts- Dean's Office, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Tisch School of Arts, 1976-1984 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Title II-A, II-C, 1981-1984 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Town Hall, 1979-1983 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Turnstiles, 1963 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Typewriters, 1961-1972 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - U.N. Depository, 1967-1979 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Undergraduate, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Undesignated Fund, 1963-1965 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - University Heights, 1965-1970 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - University Libraries Fund, 1949-1964 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - University-Wide Planning Committee, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - United Nations Collection Statistics, 1963-1970 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - United Way Fund- NYU Community Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - United Fund Campaign, 1973-1984 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - University Patents, Inc., 1982 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Union's Petition to NLRB for an election, 1978-1985 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Urban Studies Ctr., 1979-1981 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Users, Bobst, 1966-1974 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - User Policy, 1971-1974 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - User Policy Statement, 1972-1978 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Vertical File Committee, 1970-1973 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Victorian Periodicals, 1981-1983 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Visitors, 1973-1975 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - WSC- Undergraduate Library Committee, 1975-1981 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Washington Square Architectural Plans, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Washington Square Association, 1986 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Washington Square Clean-Up Oct. 1986 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Washington Square News Ad Hoc Committee, 1983-1984 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Washginton Square News- Responses, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Weather Emergency, 1981-1986 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Wenner-Gren, 1979-1990 (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Withdrawal Distributions, 1973 (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Word Processing Center, 1979 (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Xerox, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Series II: Development and Events, 1947-1995
  - ACE Greenberg, 1987 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Acquisition Virginia Woolf Collection, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Agnelli Foundation Gift, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Beverly Sprague Allen Fund, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Altshuler, Robert Collection, 1985-1990 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Altshuler, Robert Jazz Collection, 1985-1987 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Weekend, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - American Institution Program, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - American Musical Theater Archives, 1980 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - American Nobel Information Centre, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Apple Company Inc, 1993 (Box 11, File 11)
  - Apple Info Project, 1988-1990 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Apple Library of Tomorrow ALOT, 1989-1990 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - ARA Services, 1985 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Archbold Charitable Trust, 1985-1989 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - ARL "On-line Catalog Study", 1982-1984 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Arnold, Mrs. Marie B., 1966-1973 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Arthur Z. Arnold Memorial Fund, 1970-1979 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Arthur Collection of Clocks and Watches, 1983-1986 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Asner, Ed: Labor Forum Series, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Vincent Astor Foundation, 1991-1994 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Atran Foundation, 1978 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Auden Festival, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Avery Fisher Center Dinner, 1986 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Benton Foundation, 1982-1992 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Bicentenial Constitution, 1989-1995 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Bidart, Frank: Reading, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Black College Project, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Black Network Colleges, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Blaufarb Memorial, 1981 (Box 11, Folder 29)
    Separated Materials note
    Contact sheets moved to Contact Sheets- 3/5000's-3/8000's
  - Bobcat, 1984 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Bobcat Press Conference Remarks, 1983 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Bobst Awards, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Bobst Awards, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Bobst Awards: Ceremony, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 34)
    Some materials moved to Contact Sheets- 90-001 -- 90-239
  - Bobst Awards: Ceremony, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Bobst Awards: Correspondence, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Bobst Awards: Correspondence, 1991-1992 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Bobst Awards: Correspondence, 1988-1989 (Box 11, Folder 38)
  - Bobst Awards: Correspondence, 1989 (Box 11, Folder 39)
  - Bobst Awards: Dictionary of Literary Biography Yearbook, 1985-1991 (Box 11, Folder 40)
  - Bobst Awards: Emerging Writers, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 41)
  - Bobst Awards: Emerging Writers, 1991-1993 (Box 11, Folder 42)
  - Bobst Awards: Emerging Writers Selection, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 43)
  - Bobst Awards: External Correspondence, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 44)
  - Bobst Awards: Guest List, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 45)
  - Bobst Awards: Guest List, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 46)
  - Bobst Awards: Guest List, 1983-1990 (Box 11, Folder 47)
  - Bobst Awards: Guest List, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 48)
  - Bobst Awards: Honoree Biographies, 1990 (Box 11, Folder 49)
  - Bobst Awards: Internal Memoranda, 1988 (Box 11, Folder 50)
  - Bobst Awards: Jury, Nominatios and Logistics, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 51)
  - Bobst Awards: Logistics, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 52)
  - Bobst Awards: Logistics, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Bobst Awards: Logistics, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Bobst Awards: Money, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Bobst Awards: Nominees, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Bobst Awards: Politics and Internal Correspondence, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Bobst Awards: Press Coverage, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Bobst Awards: Publicity, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Bobst Awards: Publicity, 1991-1992 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Bobst Awards: Rejection Letters, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Bobst Awards: Requests, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Bobst Awards: Selection Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Bobst Awards: Speeches, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Bobst Awards: Support Letters, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Bobst New Yorker Reception, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Bobst Winners Bio Info, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Book Endowment Fund, 1977-1988 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Jessie W. Boutillier, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Brademas Speech on Libraries, Moscow, 1981 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Bunt, George, 1985-1987 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Burton, Ann M., 1993 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Bush, Maurice, 1985-1986 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Business Library, 1986-1990 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Canadian Studies, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Canadian Writers Program, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Canemaker, John: Reception, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - CARE Project, 1983 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Carey, Peter: Reading, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Case Statements and General Proposals, 1969-1972 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - CBS News Broadcasts, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Cesar Chavez Material, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Chambre, Ernest L, Collection, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Coles Service Foundation, 1972-1989 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Convocation Book by NYU Press, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Council of Fellows, 1975-1977 (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Council on Library Resources, 1983-1990 (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Crouse Publishing Library Collection, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - "Criticism at the Crossroads" Lubin Symposium, 1984-1985 (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - John Cotton Dana Award, 1984-1989 (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - "Dana" Public Relations Award, 1984 (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Danilov- General and Log- Russian Related, 1987-1988 (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Data Processing Clerk, 1988-1989 (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Dean's Review, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Development Correspondence: A-D, 1971-1996 (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Development Correspondence E-H, 1973-1995 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Development Correspondence: J-N, 1968-1990 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Development Correspondence: O-R, 1967-1985 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Development Correspondence: S-Z, 1970-1991 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Development: General, 1981-1986 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Dial-A-600, 1984-1987 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Dial-A-600- Sequel, 1987-1989 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Distinguished Books, Distinguished People, 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Edelman, Mrs. Irvin (Ethel), 1966-1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Edison Papers Project, 1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Electronic Publishing, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Endowed Chair for Dean of Libraries, 1972-1980 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Events, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Faculty Announcements, 1989-1990 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Fales Lecture- Vendler, 1992 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Fernald, Henry B., 1949-1966 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Fisher Commemorative Photo Information AFC, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Fischer Lawn Tennis, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - First Editions Club, 1971-1973 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Bob Fosse Collection, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - French Collection Endowment, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Johnson/Foster Luncheon, 1979-1982 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - French Revolution Collections, 1988-1989 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Friel, Charlotte (Papers), 1973 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Friends Reading- John A. Williams, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - "Friends of Bobst Library" Reading Series", 1985-1986 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Friends of the Bobst Library"Reading Series" Diane Ackerman and William Pitt Root, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Friends of Bobst Library "Reading Series" Mark Rudman, 1987 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Friends Reading- Stanley Kunitz- Poetics Institute, 1986 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Fussell, Paul: Speaking Engagement, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Gale Research Awards, 1985 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Geoffrey T. Hellman: The New Yorker at NYU Exhibition, 1983 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Gifts, A-F, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Gifts, G-H, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Gifts, I-L, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Gifts, M-Q, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Gifts, R-Z, 1970-1975 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Gifts- A, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Gifts- B, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Gifts- C, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Gifts- D, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Gifts- E, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Gifts- F, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Gifts-G, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Gifts- H, 1978-1988 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Gifts- I-J, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Gifts- K, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Gifts- L, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Gifts- M, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Gifts- N, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Gifts- O-Q, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Gifts- R, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Gifts- S, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Gifts- T, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Gifts- U-V, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Gifts- W-Z, 1978-1988 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Gifts: Correspondence, 1947-1959 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Gifts: Correspondence, 1947-1959 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Gifts Correspondence, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Gifts Correspondence, 1964-1969 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Gifts Miscellaneous Info, 1968-1981 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Gioia, Dana: Speaking Engagement, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Guilio Andreotti Book Party, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Global Classroom Journalism Project, 1988-1989 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Global Classroom Project, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Goldsmith Dinner, 1993 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Gordon, Mary: Reading, 1989 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Graduate Programs in Italian Life and Institutions, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Greenwich House, 1984-1989 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Harburg Foundation - NYU's Living Archive of Musical Theatre, 1982-1990 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Harburg Foundation, 1980-1988 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Hass, Robert: Reading, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Hayden-Findley, Lynn Gift, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Hazen, Joseph H. Foundation, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Hebraica and Judaica Fundraising, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Hellenic Center, 1987-1991 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Hellenic Heritage Association, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Heller and Cantor Reading- '60's Revisited, 1985 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Hellman Collection, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Hewitt, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Honorary Degrees- Speeches Examples, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Humanities Council Cirricular Challenge, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Humanities Council Cirricular Challenge, 1990 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - International Celebration, 1988 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - International Television Satellite Project, 1987-1989 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - International Television Satellite Project, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - International Television Satellite Project, 1987-1988 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Irish Studies Publishing Program, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Jamaica Kincaid, 1984 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - The Japan Foundation, 1995 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Javitz Collection, 1974-1981 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Javitz Papers, 1965-1979 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Jazz Collections, 1991-1992 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Jazz Collections - Bernie Brightman Gift, 1991-1993 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Jazz Collections - Press Stuff and Lists, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Jazz Films - Eiko and Coma, 1986-1991 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Jewish Cultural Foundation, 1965-1975 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Jewish Labor Committee, 1986-1989 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Jewish Labor Committee Background Information (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Jewish Labor Committee Collection, 1990-1991 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Jewish Labor Committee Project, 1986-1989 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Jewish Labor Committee Project Fundraising, 1986-1991 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Johnson, Philip and Richard Foster- Library Deans Council Lunch, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Judaica-Hebraica Collection, 1972-1983 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Henry J. Kaiser Foundation, 1988-1991 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Kanof, Abram: Gift, 1972-1973 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Keneally, Thomas: Reading, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Kurzweil Reading Machine, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - LeFrak, Samuel, 1994-1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
  - Lennon, John- Collection, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 10)
  - Library Gifts, 1961-1983 (Box 16, Folder 11)
  - Library of Hebraica and Judaica (Gottesman Proposal), 1972 (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - Lincolniana, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 13)
  - Literacy, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 14)
  - Literary Teas, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Living Book Endowment, 1973-1981 (Box 16, Folder 16)
  - Lowe, Joe and Emily Foundation, 1989-1994 (Box 16, Folder 17)
  - Lubin Symposia, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 18)
  - Lubin Symposia: Criticisn at Crossroad- Information on Panelists, 1981-1984 (Box 16, Folder 19)
  - Lubin Symposia: Hugging the Shore, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - Lubin Symposium, 1984-1985 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Manhattan College Working File, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Marshall, Herbert- Archive, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 23)
  - Matthews, William Reading, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Mediating History Party, 1990-1992 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Morris, Mary and Bharati Mukherjee, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Moscow State University, 1987 (Box 16, Folder 27)
  - Murphy, George A., 1985-1989 (Box 16, Folder 28)
  - Musical Theatre Archives, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - Near East Collection, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - Norman, Isabel and Nathaniel, 1988 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - NYU Classics Notecards, 1990-1991 (Box 16, Folder 32)
  - NYU Cirricular Development Challenge Fund, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 33)
  - O'Neil, Hank, 1992 (Box 16, Folder 34)
  - Optical Disc Equipment, 1987-1988 (Box 16, Folder 35)
  - Papamark, Alexander, 1993-1998 (Box 17, File 1)
  - Performing Arts Collection, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Pforzheimer, C.H., Jr., 1970-1972 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Pinsky, Robert- Reading, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Porter. Fairfield; Tribute "The Man in Blue: Fairfield Porter and Poetry", 1984 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Potential Donation: Film Collection, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Prospect Tracking Records, 1971-1984 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Raasch, John E. and Helen K Libraries Foundation, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Reader's Digest Award, 1993 (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Real Estate Library Project, 1983-1991 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Reports/Individuals, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Rich. Adrienne- Reading, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Ricks, Christopher- Fales Lecture, 1990 (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Robinson, Earl- Dinner, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - "Romare Bearden" Working File '89, 1977-1989 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Richard and Hinda Rosenthal Foundation, 1990-1993 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Russia Bills, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Library, Danilov Monastery: Equipment, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Russian Orthodox Church Library, Danilov Monastery: Proposals, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Russian Orthodox Church, Danilov Monastery: Proposals and Research, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 20)
  - Salute to Our Neighbors, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Salute to Our Neighbors Gala Event, 1985-1986 (Box 17, Folder 22)
  - Sanchez, Sonia- Reading, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Shachtman, Max- Reception, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 24)
  - Schechner Collection, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 25)
  - Schechner Performance Group Archives, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 26)
  - Seeger/Protest Music, 1983-1984 (Box 17, Folder 27)
  - Sesquicentennial Oral History Program, 1979 (Box 17, Folder 28)
  - Sesquicentennial Reception, 1981-1982 (Box 17, Folder 29)
  - Simpson, Louis- Reading, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 30)
  - Simpson, Mona- Reading, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Sinatra, Frank, 1985-1987 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - Singer, Dr. Henry American Nobel Committee, 1992 (Box 17, Folder 33)
  - Singer, Isaac Collection, 1986-1994 (Box 17, Folder 34)
  - Society for the Libraries, 1969-1981 (Box 17, Folder 35)
  - Society for the Library, 1970-1988 (Box 17, Folder 36)
  - South Manhattan Consortium, 1977-1978 (Box 17, Folder 37)
  - Soviet Libraries, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 38)
  - Soviet Union- Repentance, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 39)
  - Special Collections Wing Opening, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 40)
  - Special Events, 1991 (Box 17, Folder 41)
  - Special Events, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 42)
  - Speigel, Sam- Archives, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 43)
  - Stanley Elkin- File of Asst to Dean, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 44)
  - Stern, Sidney Memorial Trust, 1986-1994 (Box 17, Folder 45)
  - Stern and Fox Readings, 1989 (Box 17, Folder 46)
  - Sulzberger, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 47)
  - Supplementary Mailing List Library Events, 1984-1985 (Box 17, Folder 48)
  - Support for Public Schools, 1987-1988 (Box 17, Folder 49)
  - Talking Bobcat, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 50)
  - Television Commercials Archives, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 51)
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1970-1976 (Box 17, Folder 52)
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1969-1976 (Box 17, Folder 53)
  - Thomson, Virgil, 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 54)
  - Todman, William S. and Fran, 1984-1991 (Box 17, Folder 55)
  - Tracy Barry Gallery, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - Turkish Collection/Ahmet Ertegun, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 56)
  - University Archives (development project), 1981 (Box 17, Folder 57)
  - University of Tennessee Knoxville, 1987-1989 (Box 17, Folder 58)
  - Wagner Archives Reception, 1983-1990 (Box 17, Folder 59)
  - Warner - Lambert Co., 1972-1985 (Box 17, Folder 61)
  - Weill Archives, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 62)
  - Kurt Weill Foundation, 1981 (Box 17, Folder 63)
  - Weiss, Raymond, 1996-1997 (Box 17, Folder 64)
  - Wenner-Gren Foundation, 1979-1980 (Box 17, Folder 65)
  - Women's Studies Collection, 1988 (Box 17, Folder 66)
  - Woolf, Virginia- Reading, 1987 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Wozniak, Henry P., 1987 (Box 17, Folder 68)
  - Xerox Corp - Corporate Donors, 1982 (Box 17, Folder 69)
  - Zizes, Helen and Alvin Philanthropic Fund (Jewish Federation/Palm Beach Co.), 1988 (Box 17, Folder 70)
- Series III: Budget and Planning, 1966-1983
  - 3rd Floor, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - 9th Floor, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - 10th Floor, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - 11th Floor, 1972-1974 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Academic Library Survey- Tech II, 1968-1972 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Architecture, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Bobst- Building, Equipment, Maintenance, Action Pending, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Bobst- Level A, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Bobst Library Budget, 1978-1979 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Bobst Library Budget, 1972-1980 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Bobst Library Budget, 1977-1978 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Bobst Library- Memos, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Bobst Library- planning, invoices, 1973 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Bobst Library- planning, space, furniture, 1972-1973 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Bobst Security, 1973-1977 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Bobst- Steel Inventory, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Bobst- Wood Equipment, 1972-1975 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Budget, 1975-1976 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Budget, 1976-1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)